[Music]
charisma Jeneva paper would have
international people dr. Bini crumble
menu like Cambodia Morocco paramshanti
McClure Nelson tacky or a followed out
to the point
[Music]
Milman men Clanton chica opposite oku
pranam robot revolt Anita braggadocios
menu like Cambodia penalty by Koji
savage attack
who'sa had come to New Roman ogee was
bandaged Luca concrete a Kampuchea
proposed a positive ROI Chaka Khan
launched evil Dominic angel Duncan time
Prasad robot a Chechen computer systems
in Canada beyond panic ahead on the top
Sandra from Busan
[Music]
when I look back and we had no staff no
customers no brands
it was quite daunting and when I look
back now and I see that we've got over
200 staff and the staff are very
competent they are as good as any we
have in Manulife around the region their
enthusiasm their dedication and their
professionalism that's made me extremely
proud I remember our first customer back
in June 2012 and I also remember the
first 10 customers and then after three
months we had a hundred and after ten
months we had a thousand and to see now
that we're protecting over 40,000 people
gives me a tremendous amount of pride
[Music]
multiply the common form of coffee cup a
junk side video of be some at the park
Columbia pay from China milk cambogia
robot Manulife bonbon heijunka
monotectic come from crime the
Walkerville and ratchet Mooney no
cacciucco fan and I've got a hangover
Fatima Mui some rockin bizarre come to
you
[Music]
tropical soda to become company van
control logic own kombucha Tamra gets a
canopy Pinkham Notch we overcome nine
years of accrual nanu Yong su ke kanaka
maoli banjaluka book onomatopoeia and
employs over Tamla motivate Kumar men
catch I think no te amo can drop a camp
yield
Sandhya control can report on and
rigidity phenomenal and go wash it out
in the community we want to be able to
help people have a better lifestyle have
a healthier lifestyle and it really is a
wellness and well-being strategy then
those things are very important to us to
build those long-term relationships and
helping Cambodia build a better and
healthier lifestyle
Crom home in july men alkmaar low per
day canada Halmi infer what aikido
camera baccala CMOS at the bottom howie
from beneath compose mama appendage on
the balloon t-mobile in yet to tell
people blow Kampuchea Gucci purse a
console game like company wanting to
Joseph a champion wanna be aluminum
chakram hunter near a Verona do - what
contract is the bomb cable cause notice
on that he cannot Yahoo javi
[Music]
well I don't see it as competition
because the needs of the Cambodian
people are quite high and because the
penetration is so low that there is
plenty of room for lots of companies to
come into Cambodia and build a good
business as long as they are helping
Cambodian people build a better
financial future for themselves just
[Music]
transitioning people on the beach night
at muscaria Lida baklava crewmen menu
like Cambodia one fellow Jews who were
two people here anger for long attention
Kampuchea Jim Bollman mo Cowie
jamuna kappa Meridian Chopra has been
modified TomTom we don't know geo custom
religion and people on the ball had
multiple million people on the pram then
kind of bootcamp million people flock
from will
[Music]
you